[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fill in the missing words said by the Phantom in the movie The Phantom of the Opera:\nLook at your _______ in the ___________! I am there inside!", "correct_answer": "face; mirror", "incorrect_answers": ["head; sunshine", "face; Phantom", "eyes; mirror"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Measured from base to peak, what is the worlds highest mountain?", "correct_answer": "Mauna Kea", "incorrect_answers": ["Chimborazo", "K2", "Mt. Everest"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On TV, what was the name of Sergeant Prestons horse?", "correct_answer": "Rex", "incorrect_answers": ["Videl", "Max", "Hopper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the computer software company for which Peter, Michael and Samir worked in the movie Office Space?", "correct_answer": "Initech", "incorrect_answers": ["Interlode", "Penetrode", "Initrode"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Progesterone, the hormone of pregnancy, is synthesized in this part of the body.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["In the ovaries", "In the placenta", "In the brain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Borneo is the 3rd largest island in the world.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Charlies grandpa do when the little boy showed him the golden ticked he found in the candy bar in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "He started dancing.", "incorrect_answers": ["He stared crying.", "He tossed his wig.", "He fainted."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This English mathematician, logician and cryptographer is widely regarded as the father of modern computer science.", "correct_answer": "Alan Turing", "incorrect_answers": ["Max Newman", "Ada Lovelace", "John Atanasoff"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first woman to have a gold record?", "correct_answer": "Judy Garland", "incorrect_answers": ["Teresa Brewer", "Connie  Francis", "Shirley Temple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The hairs of a natural blonde can be described as this.", "correct_answer": "More than those of a brunette", "incorrect_answers": ["Thinner than those of a brunette", "The same number as those of a brunette", "Fewer than those of a brunette"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word hurricane\u201d comes from the name of a Caribbean god - Huracan. Huracan was god of what?", "correct_answer": "The storms", "incorrect_answers": ["The sea", "The weather", "The moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ancient Japanese thought this animal caused earthquakes.", "correct_answer": "Spiders", "incorrect_answers": ["Birds", "Snakes", "Frogs"]}]